<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="tooros_technologies_is_one_the_best_self_drive_car_rental_company_in_bhubaneswar_with_an_innovative_way_of_satisfying_the_requirement_of_the_car_rental_industry_it_was_finally_successfully_launched_by_two_entrepreneurs_who_are_always_interested_by_cars_if_you_love_to_travel_then_toorosself_drive_car_services_will_surely_enable_you_to_take_control_of_the_wheels_and_create_memorable_stories_on_your_travel_journey_with_tooros_you_can_drive_your_dream_car_to_your_favorite_destination_at_an_affordable_budget_our_wide_range_of_cars_includes_hatchbacks_sedans_suv_we_promise_to_deliver_you_completely_sanitized_and_well_maintained_cars_for_self_drive_car_rent_in_bhubaneswar_apart_from_this_we_also_have_a_dedicated_team_of_customers_supports_executives_who_are_available_for_you_24_7_365_days_n_nbest_things_in_life_do_not_come_with_any_usage_caps_thus_providing_unlimited_kilometers_on_every_booking_is_our_way_of_saying_it_to_consumers_with_tooros_self_drive_cars_you_drive_happiness_you_always_have_the_dual_advantage_of_freedom_privacy_that_makes_us_the_best_choice_n_nso_what_are_you_waiting_for_time_to_book_and_ride"><![CDATA[Tooros Technologies is one the best Self-drive car rental company in Bhubaneswar with an innovative way of satisfying the requirement of the car rental industry. It was finally successfully launched by two entrepreneurs who are always interested by cars. If you love to travel then ToorosSelf drive car services will surely enable you to take control of the wheels and create memorable stories on your travel journey. With tooros, you can drive your dream car to your favorite destination at an affordable budget. Our wide range of cars includes Hatchbacks, Sedans & SUV. We promise to deliver you completely Sanitized and well-maintained cars for self-drive car rent in Bhubaneswar. Apart from this we also have a dedicated team of customers supports executives who are available for you 24*7/365 days.  Best things in life do not come with any usage caps, thus providing unlimited kilometers on every booking is our way of saying it to consumers. With Tooros self-drive cars, you drive happiness; you always have the dual advantage of freedom & privacy that makes us the best choice.  So, what are you waiting for? Time to book and ride!]]></string>
</resources>